// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions3 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "My full name is Lucy Bella Simkins.",
        answer: "What is your full name?",
        options: [
          "What is your full name?",
          "How is your first name spelt?",
          "Who chose your name?",
          "Where were you born?",
          "Is it a city or a town?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 2,
        question: "L-U-C-Y, Lucy.",
        answer:
            "How is your first name spelt?",
        options: [
          "What is your full name?",
          "How is your first name spelt?",
          "Who chose your name?",
          "Where were you born?",
          "Is it a city or a town?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 3,
        question: "I think my mum did. I haven't actually asked that question before.",
        answer:
        "Who chose your name?",
        options: [
          "What is your full name?",
          "How is your first name spelt?",
          "Who chose your name?",
          "Where were you born?",
          "Is it a city or a town?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 4,
        question: "I was born in Milton Keynes in England.",
        answer:
        "Where were you born?",
        options: [
          "What is your full name?",
          "How is your first name spelt?",
          "Who chose your name?",
          "Where were you born?",
          "Is it a city or a town?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 5,
        question: "I think it's a city. They always refer to it as a city.",
        answer:
        "Is it a city or a town?",
        options: [
          "What is your full name?",
          "How is your first name spelt?",
          "Who chose your name?",
          "Where were you born?",
          "Is it a city or a town?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Yes. My favourite colour is orange.",
        answer:
        "Do you have a favourite colour?",
        options: [
          "Do you have a favourite colour?",
          "What kind of music do you listen to?",
          "Do you have a favourite musical artist?",
          "What was the last concert you went to?",
          "Do you have a favourite season?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 7,
        question: "I don't really listen to too much music. Whatever's in the charts.",
        answer:
        "What kind of music do you listen to?",
        options: [
          "Do you have a favourite colour?",
          "What kind of music do you listen to?",
          "Do you have a favourite musical artist?",
          "What was the last concert you went to?",
          "Do you have a favourite season?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 8,
        question: "I love Taylor Swift.",
        answer:
        "Do you have a favourite musical artist?",
        options: [
          "Do you have a favourite colour?",
          "What kind of music do you listen to?",
          "Do you have a favourite musical artist?",
          "What was the last concert you went to?",
          "Do you have a favourite season?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 9,
        question: "The last concert I went to was a festival when I was 20.",
        answer:
        "What was the last concert you went to?",
        options: [
          "Do you have a favourite colour?",
          "What kind of music do you listen to?",
          "Do you have a favourite musical artist?",
          "What was the last concert you went to?",
          "Do you have a favourite season?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Yes. My favourite season is spring.",
        answer:
        "Do you have a favourite season?",
        options: [
          "Do you have a favourite colour?",
          "What kind of music do you listen to?",
          "Do you have a favourite musical artist?",
          "What was the last concert you went to?",
          "Do you have a favourite season?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 11,
        question: "I love all the new life, the new leaves and the new flowers.",
        answer:
        "What do you like about that season?",
        options: [
          "What do you like about that season?",
          "How many people are in your immediate family?",
          "Do you have any siblings?",
          "How old is your sibling?",
          "How often do you see your sibling?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Do I count the dog and the cat? If so, four of us.",
        answer:
        "How many people are in your immediate family?",
        options: [
          "What do you like about that season?",
          "How many people are in your immediate family?",
          "Do you have any siblings?",
          "How old is your sibling?",
          "How often do you see your sibling?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Yes, I have a younger brother called George.",
        answer:
        "Do you have any siblings?",
        options: [
          "What do you like about that season?",
          "How many people are in your immediate family?",
          "Do you have any siblings?",
          "How old is your sibling?",
          "How often do you see your sibling?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 14,
        question: "My brother is 23.",
        answer:
        "How old is your sibling?",
        options: [
          "What do you like about that season?",
          "How many people are in your immediate family?",
          "Do you have any siblings?",
          "How old is your sibling?",
          "How often do you see your sibling?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Not as often as I'd like.",
        answer:
        "How often do you see your sibling?",
        options: [
          "What do you like about that season?",
          "How many people are in your immediate family?",
          "Do you have any siblings?",
          "How old is your sibling?",
          "How often do you see your sibling?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 16,
        question: "Yes, I'm just married.",
        answer:
        "Are you married?",
        options: [
          "Are you married?",
          "How would you describe your husband?",
          "How old were your parents when they got married?",
          "Do you have children?",
          "Do you plan to have children?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 17,
        question: "Lovely, handsome, very tall and very funny.",
        answer:
        "How would you describe your husband?",
        options: [
          "Are you married?",
          "How would you describe your husband?",
          "How old were your parents when they got married?",
          "Do you have children?",
          "Do you plan to have children?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 18,
        question: "My mum was 24 and my dad was 28.",
        answer:
        "How old were your parents when they got married?",
        options: [
          "Are you married?",
          "How would you describe your husband?",
          "How old were your parents when they got married?",
          "Do you have children?",
          "Do you plan to have children?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 19,
        question: "No.",
        answer:
        "Do you have children?",
        options: [
          "Are you married?",
          "How would you describe your husband?",
          "How old were your parents when they got married?",
          "Do you have children?",
          "Do you plan to have children?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 20,
        question: "I would love to have children.",
        answer:
        "Do you plan to have children?",
        options: [
          "Are you married?",
          "How would you describe your husband?",
          "How old were your parents when they got married?",
          "Do you have children?",
          "Do you plan to have children?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 21,
        question: "My father works with sports pitches.",
        answer:
        "What does your father do for work?",
        options: [
          "What does your father do for work?",
          "What does your mum do for work?",
          "What do your parents do for fun?",
          "How would you describe your parents?",
          "Where do you currently live?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 22,
        question: "My mother was a swimming teacher.",
        answer:
        "What does your mum do for work?",
        options: [
          "What does your father do for work?",
          "What does your mum do for work?",
          "What do your parents do for fun?",
          "How would you describe your parents?",
          "Where do you currently live?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 23,
        question: "My parents love spending time with the family.",
        answer:
        "What do your parents do for fun?",
        options: [
          "What does your father do for work?",
          "What does your mum do for work?",
          "What do your parents do for fun?",
          "How would you describe your parents?",
          "Where do you currently live?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 24,
        question: "Hilarious, lovely, wonderful.",
        answer:
        "How would you describe your parents?",
        options: [
          "What does your father do for work?",
          "What does your mum do for work?",
          "What do your parents do for fun?",
          "How would you describe your parents?",
          "Where do you currently live?"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 25,
        question: "I currently live in the Cotswolds.",
        answer:
        "Where do you currently live?",
        options: [
          "What does your father do for work?",
          "What does your mum do for work?",
          "What do your parents do for fun?",
          "How would you describe your parents?",
          "Where do you currently live?"
        ]
      },
        
// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];